一旦适配器被初始化  让我们把它绑定到ListView列表控件
Once the adapter is initialized, let's bind it to the list view. But
但是你可能注意到了在我们的布局中没有提及到ListView列表控件
you may notice that we don't have a reference to the list view in our fragment.
它仅仅是定义在layout XML文件中的  系统会使用并添加
It was only defined in the layout XML. The system takes and
layout XML文件  并且
inflates layout XML files. And
把它们转到一个在视图树顶部的带有一个主activity的根layout完整的视图分层
turns them into a full view hierarchy with a root layout of the main activity at
我们也可以指定ID到树中的每个视图
the very top of the view tree. We can also assign IDs to each view in the tree,
如果你不需要ID来参考那么就不是必要的
but it's not required if you don't need a reference to an individual view.
举个例子  这个图像视图没有与之关联的ID  也是可以的
For example, this image view doesn't have an ID associated with it and
与activity或布局相关联的Java代码同样包含
that's okay. Within the Java code of the associated activity or
如果我们需要一个按钮的引用  我们可以使用findViewByID来完成
fragment. If we need a reference to the button, we can simply call findViewById,
它会遍历树下面的层次结构直到它找到带有button的视图
which will traverse down the hierarchy until it finds a view with the ID button.
然后它会返回  同样的  我们可以遍历树下面的视图层次
And then it will return that. Similarly, we can traverse down the view
去寻找带有container ID的线性的layouts并返回
hierarchy to find the linear layout with the ID container, and then return that.
我们同样可以使用参照去找到TextView通过树向下遍历视图层次结构
We could do the same to find a reference to this TextView by traversing down
但是你会注意到我们已经有了一个container的参考
the view hierarchy. But you'll notice that we already have a reference to
并且TextView是container的子树  因此
the container which is a direct parent of this TextView. Hence, we can just call
因此我们可以直接使用container.findViewById去搜索子树并寻找带有这个ID的TextView
container.findViewById to search this subtree to find the TextView with this ID,
并且返回它  使用这个方法  我们用一个更小的子树
and then return it. With this method, we have a smaller sub-tree to search for
去搜索一个给定的视图而不是去搜索整个View的结构
a given view, as opposed to searching the entire view hierarchy.
在Android Java文档中对于View这个类的说明  如果你也想这样做
In the Android Java doc for the View class, which is linked below if you want to
在下面有文档的链接  它包含一个在Layout XML文档中定义过的按钮的例子
follow along, it contains an example where the button with Define in Layout XML.
这是一个已经分配过的my_button的ID  然后在Activity当中
It was assigned an ID My Button. Then in the Activity, we can use the find
我们可以使用通过查找ID的方法查找view  有了那个ID  我们可以得到它的返回值
view by ID method, with that ID, so that we can get a reference to the button.
然后我们可以动态地改变它  例如添加一个点击监听器来改变
Then we can change it dynamically, such as by adding a click listener to it.
现在在占位符布局的类中  将适配器绑定到ListView
Now in the placeholder fragment class, bind the adapter to the list view.
幸运的是  我们已经给ListView分配了一个ID  所以我们可以很容易的找到它
Luckily, we did assign an ID to the list view earlier. So, we can find it
想想你可以在视图层次中可以调用ID查找视图的最小的树
easily now. Think about the smallest sub-tree in the view hierarchy that you
并在上面设置一个适配器  如果你想要一个例子
can call find view by ID on. Then set the adapter on it. If you want an example,
你可以在下面的链接中看到  当你完成的时候请勾选复选框
you can see one in the link below. Check the boxes when you're done.